Juan Francisco Perez

"I've been passionate about computers since I was a kid. I have always been a very curious and self-taught person. I have participated in several projects since my time as a student and after finishing my degree. I have experience as SysAdmin, DevOps and as Coordinator of Technical and Administrative Teams."

Gorriti 213 7mo Depto 25 4600 San Salvador de Jujuy. +(54) 3884802323 yojota@gmail.com https://yojota.com.ar

Advanced Skill

GNU/Linux, Sistem Administrator, DNS, Email, Public Cloud (AWS), MySQL, and deep knowledge in computer science.

Experiences

Silentium Apps: SRE - DevOps

July 2021 - Present

CI/CD in docker environment. AWS – Azure – On–premise. Jenkins. Github Action.

Edrans, Buenos Aires: Site Operation.

September of 2020 - June 2021

The first point of contact to external worldwide customers, also you will be helping to identify, analyze and resolve first-tier technical issues on large scale productive platforms.

Valerza S. A., Jujuy: Technology Manager.

September of 2018 - September 2020

Project Leader. Product Architect. management of various projects for the different business units.

Projects

NicromIT: Cloud Solutions – DevOps Culture.

CEO. In charge of customer contact. Project manager. Sysadmin Linux. DevOps Team Support

Education

Universidad Catolica de Santiago del Estero: IT Engineering

March of 2003 - November del 2011 Complete

Strengths

Self-taught

Restless

Good teamwork

Good communication

Ease to communicate with non-technical equipment.

Additional Activities

Proyecto Pachado Secure Wifi connection with certificates 2011

Founder: Grupo de usuarios de software libre de Jujuy.

Tutor: Introduction to free software. Duration 1 year.

Exhibitor and Speaker: In different free software events in the province and throughout the country.

Languages

Spanish (native).

English (intermediate certificate by Global21).

Technical Skills	
Sysadmin GNU Linux	****
Scripting python, bash, php	***
Docker	***
Kubernetes	*
Terraform (IaaC)	***
AWS	***
Google Cloud	*
Mail Server	****
KVM (Kernel Virtual Machine)	****
Virtualization	***
Management Tools and Project (Trello, Jira, Zenkit, Confluence, etc)	* *****
DNS	****
Firewall	***
Microsoft environment	**
Ansible	**
Git	****
Github Action	***
Jenkins	***
Other Skills	
Handling of technical and non-technical equipment	
Vendor Management	
Payment and collection management	

I have been **working remotely** for more than two years. I have experience working at night. In the last few years I have worked with clients around the world.